<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coach Colemere</title>
    <description>Bryan Colemere, a top Real Estate Agent in Utah, shares his/her own internal real estate agent training for free. His/Her Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:11:41 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:11:41 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Checking in With Top Producer Lorna Davis</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nK0TgTYhoz0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lorna Davis recently sat down to share some of her success secrets with us. Watch our interview here!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Colemere Realty is proud to have so many top-producing agents working as part of our team, and today we’ve decided to feature just one of these incredible professionals: &lt;u&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.colemererealty.com/agents/137015-Lorna-Davis/&quot;&gt;Lorna Davis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a mother and a real estate professional, Lorna makes it a priority to keep her work-life balance in check, and the results have been astounding. On top of having an incredible family, Lorna has doubled her business each year since joining Colemere Realty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To learn more about Lorna and her many successes, feel free to watch today’s interview in full or to browse the video at your leisure using the timestamps we’ve cited below:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:29 - What did Lorna do before starting her real estate career, and why did she make the switch?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:05 - How has Lorna been able to increase her business over time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:35 - How does delegating tasks and dividing time between one’s personal and professional life help improve their overall performance?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:54 - What does a day in Lorna’s life look like?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:54 - Why did Lorna change brokerages and join our team?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5:39 - How does Lorna get leads?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:59 - A few closing words from Lorna&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions, would like more information, or are interested in learning more about what it’s like to work with Colemere Realty, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/checking-in-with-top-producer-lorna-davis.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/checking-in-with-top-producer-lorna-davis.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Practices for Increasing Your Conversion Rates</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/B3kHIE5PQcU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today I&amp;rsquo;ll discuss key tips to help you increase your conversion rates. Here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to know.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first thing to know about converting leads is that you’re not going to be very good at it if you don’t practice. By that, I mean &lt;strong&gt;you need to practice your scripts&lt;/strong&gt;. Pay attention to your tonality—how fast or slow you speak plays a huge role in your ability to connect with people and to earn their trust and loyalty. If you sound unknowledgeable or aggressive on the phone, the person you’re talking to isn’t going to want to do business with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who do you want to do business with? People who respect you and your time and pay you a commission that you’re worth, or someone who will beat you up the whole time and tell you that you’re awful?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, &lt;strong&gt;you should always seek out critiques&lt;/strong&gt; so that you can identify how you can do better. Record yourself as you make calls so you can go back and listen to them. Trust me, that might be extremely painful, but it’s better than remaining in the dark about your own shortcomings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Pay attention to your tonality—how fast or slow you speak plays a huge role in your ability to connect with people and to earn their trust and loyalty.%20http://localhost:4000/best-practices-for-increasing-your-conversion-rates.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Pay attention to your tonality—how fast or slow you speak plays a huge role in your ability to connect with people and to earn their trust and loyalty.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It might also be worthwhile to do some type of group calling effort in which you call live leads as a group. This way, someone with experience can help you as you make your calls. Practice calls are very different from actual live calls, after all. Having someone there to guide and direct you through the process of talking to leads will ultimately help you land an appointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That in mind, &lt;strong&gt;I’m inviting you to our call hours&lt;/strong&gt;, which we hold four times a week. There, we call live leads as a group to help each other improve our conversion skills. If you’re interested in attending, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to have you participate so that you can improve your conversion rates and grow your business.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/best-practices-for-increasing-your-conversion-rates.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/best-practices-for-increasing-your-conversion-rates.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Holding Real Estate Agents Accountable for Their Own Success</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IYDIw8s5np8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;It can be hard to hold yourself accountable in real estate, but Colemere Realty has a system to help.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the key things we’ve identified is that &lt;strong&gt;it’s always easy to take the path of least resistance&lt;/strong&gt;. Every agent knows that the volume of your closings depends on how many contracts you write, which in turn depends on how many people you talk to. How many people you talk to depends on how many phone calls or conversations you have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that sense, real estate is not that hard, but for some reason, agents often build up the mindset that it is hard to talk to people, or that we’re too busy to do the work it takes to get contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=It’s extremely difficult to hold yourself accountable.%20http://localhost:4000/holding-real-estate-agents-accountable-for-their-own-success.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“It’s extremely difficult to hold yourself accountable.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team has been very successful in holding our agents accountable. &lt;strong&gt;Each week, we hold a one-on-one meeting with our accountability coach&lt;/strong&gt;. Her job is to identify the key areas in which you’re doing well, as well as the areas you can improve upon. She’ll help you track how many calls you make, the quality of your follow-ups with leads, and how many people you’re talking to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s extremely difficult to hold yourself accountable, and if you don’t believe me, go ahead and try. If you can do it, I’d love to hear about your methods, because at any and all levels in real estate, I’ve seen agents struggling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to see how we do our one-on-ones or get a copy of our accountability matrix, please reach out to us. We’d be happy to provide that for you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/holding-real-estate-agents-accountable-for-their-own-success.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/holding-real-estate-agents-accountable-for-their-own-success.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Importance of Having a Lead Follow-Up System</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FYo3ISOzm_I?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t implemented a lead follow-up system into your real estate business, you&amp;rsquo;re doing yourself a disservice.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the last 66 years that our team has been in business, we’ve developed a powerful set of systems that enable us to thrive; and, now, we’d like to pass some of that wisdom on to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically, we want to offer some insight into our lead follow-up process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The first thing we recommend is to utilize a CRM, like &lt;a href=&quot;https://boomtownroi.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BoomTown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Organizing your leads using CRM software will help you keep track of which leads you’ve recently spoken to, which leads you should nurture, and which leads are most likely to convert at a given moment, among other things. Within our own lead follow-up system, we place leads into seven categories: new, qualify, hot, watch, nurture, archive, and trash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s important to put as many people as possible into this lead “funnel.”&lt;/strong&gt; Doing so will give you a consistent stream of business. Of course, you’ll need to make this process as automated as possible if you want to have time to work on other areas of your business, as well. This is why lead follow-up software systems are so important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you haven’t invested in some sort of follow-up system, you’re leaving business (and money) on the table.%20http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-having-a-lead-follow-up-system.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you haven’t invested in some sort of follow-up system, you’re leaving business (and money) on the table.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it’s still important for you to do some hands-on work, like making phone calls and sending text messages. After all, you want these leads to know you’re available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A number of studies have shown that most leads will only convert after they’ve received between eight and 11 touches from an agent&lt;/strong&gt;. Calling once or twice won’t cut it. If you haven’t invested in some sort of follow-up system, you’re leaving business (and money) on the table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully today’s message has been enlightening. If you have any other questions or would like more information about growing your business, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-having-a-lead-follow-up-system.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-having-a-lead-follow-up-system.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The 3 Lead Generation Techniques We Utilize</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nncyVFHe9YU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our lead generation techniques help us stay at the top. Here&amp;rsquo;s what we do.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can’t stay in business for 66 years without having some great strategies and systems in place. What drives us is simple: lead generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We teach our agents that there are three types of leads they should be working each day:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Sphere of influence&lt;/strong&gt;. Many agents don’t put the members of their sphere into a database, and then they’re unable to contact them systematically. Without an organized approach, it’s difficult to receive repeat clients and referrals. We show our agents how to automate and use these powerful sources of business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=These are just a few ways that we take advantage of powerful lead generation strategies.%20http://localhost:4000/the-3-lead-generation-techniques-we-utilize.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“These are just a few ways that we take advantage of powerful lead generation strategies.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Outbound prospecting&lt;/strong&gt;. This can be done through FSBOs, expired listings, open houses, door knocking, and simply calling around the neighborhood. We provide agents the scripts and show them how to follow up and convert leads into clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Internet leads&lt;/strong&gt;. We invest heavily in online sources and teach agents how to properly connect with them, talk with them, and convert them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are just a few ways that we take advantage of powerful lead generation strategies; stay tuned for even more! In the meantime, If you have any questions or would like more information, feel free to reach out to us. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-3-lead-generation-techniques-we-utilize.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-3-lead-generation-techniques-we-utilize.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Will Agents Learn From Our New Recruiting Blog?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/QMhSRPgX7YM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve been selling real estate for 66 years, so we know what it takes to have staying power in this business. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to create this real estate career blog.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our company has been selling real estate for the last 66 years, so we’ve recently decided to start a real estate career blog called “Utah Real Estate Top Producers.” We’ve noticed that a lot of agents have struggled in the last five to 10 years because of changing market conditions. Each month, we’re going to showcase a new topic and detail what we’ve done to become successful as a team. We’ll cover topics such as leads, lead conversion, accountability, coaching, mentorship, changing market conditions, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-will-agents-learn-from-our-new-recruiting-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-will-agents-learn-from-our-new-recruiting-blog.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
